semi.org 2019-12-22

# SEMI Privacy Policy | SEMI

  * **SEMI Website Properties Terms of Use**
  * **SEMI Website Properties  Privacy Policy**
  * **SEMI Academic Privacy Policy**
  * **SEMI Academic Website Terms of Use**

### PRIVACY POLICY

EFFECTIVE DATE: May 25, 2018

In this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), we describe how SEMI (“SEMI” or the “Company”) of 673 S Milpitas Blvd, Milpitas, CA 95035 collects, uses, and discloses information that we obtain about visitors to our website, www.semi.org (the “Site”), users of our mobile Application (our “App”), and the services available through our Site and App (collectively, the “Services”), and how we use and disclose that information.  SEMI's representative in the European Union is SEMI Europe of Helmholtzstrasse 2-9  
House D / 3rd floor, 10587 Berlin, Germany.

By visiting the Site, using or downloading our App, or otherwise using our Services, you acknowledge that your personal information will be handled as described in this Policy. Your use of our Site, App, or Services, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Service, including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes. Our Terms of Service are incorporated by reference into this Policy.

The Information We Collect About You  
Information We Collect Directly From You  
Information We Collect Automatically  
How We Use Your Information  
How We Share Your Information  
Our Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms  
Clear GIFs, pixel tags and other technologies  
Third Party Analytics  
Third-Party Ad Networks  
Third-Party Links  
Security of My Personal Information  
Access To My Personal Information  
What Rights and Choices Do I Have Regarding Use of My Personal Information?  
Children Under 13  
Contact Us  
Changes to this Policy

### The Information We Collect About You

We collect information about you directly from you, from third parties, and automatically through your use of our Site, App, and Services.

### Information We Collect Directly From You 

The scope of information that we collect about you depends on your interaction with our services. If you register with us, we will collect your:  email, country/region, language preference, first name, last name, and information about your communications preferences. You have the option to provide us with additional information, including, your title, company, address, phone, fax, job function, job level. We also collect information from you when you contact us through our Site or App, download a whitepaper, submit a paper, attend one of our events, or otherwise interact with our Services.  In addition, if you make a purchase, such as purchasing access to a webinar, we will also request that you provide your credit or debit card information and your billing and shipping address.

### Information We Collect Automatically 

We automatically collect the following information about your use of our Services through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies, including tracking technologies designed for mobile devices:  your domain name; your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your IP address; the length of time you visit our Site and/or use our Services; and the referring URL, or the webpage that led you to our Site. 

We also collect the following information about your use of the App:  mobile device ID; location and language information; device name and model; operating system type, name, and version; your activities within the App; and the length of time that you are logged into our App. 

We may combine this information with other information that we have collected about you, including, where applicable, your user name, name, and other personal information.  Please see the section “Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms” below for more information.

Information We Collect From Third Parties/Public Sources. If your employer registers you for one of our products or Services, then we collect the information that your employer provides to us. Members also may post press releases on our Site; such releases may contain your name as a contact point.

**_If You Do Not Provide Information_** If we need to collect your personal information for legal reasons, or under the terms of a contract or to enter into a contract with you, and you fail to provide that information then we may be limited as to the Services we can provide and in our performance of the contract and if there is a legal impact we will seek to explain this further to you]

### How We Use Your Information

We use your information, including your personal information, for the following purposes:

  * To provide our Services to you, to communicate with you about your use of our Services, to respond to your inquiries, to fulfill your orders, and for other customer service purposes.
  * To tailor the content and information that we may send or display to you, to offer location customization, and personalized help and instructions, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using our Services.
  * As permitted by local law, for marketing and promotional purposes. Specifically, we use your information to send you news and newsletters, special offers, and promotions, or to otherwise contact you about products or information we think may interest you.
  * As permitted by local law, to gain insight into how users interact with our Services, which may assist us in determining appropriate advertising on our Site or on third party websites.
  * To better understand how users access and use our Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis
  * To improve our Services
  * For research purposes, such as to research industry trends related to our Services

If you are in the European Union (EU), when we process personal data about you in the context of our  activities established in the EU or related to our offering of goods or services to you or our monitoring of your behavior within the EU (“EU Processing”) we will do so only when the law allows us.  In most cases we or our third parties will be processing your personal data where it is necessary: (a) for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) where these do not override your own interests, rights and freedoms: and our legitimate interests are the furtherance of (i) our mission to provide industry stewardship and engage our members to advance the interests of the global electronics supply chain and (ii) our vision to promote the development of the global electronics supply chain and positively influence the growth and prosperity of our  members, advancing the mutual business interests of our membership and promoting a free and open global marketplace - including through the development, operation and promotion of our Services; or (b) to perform a contract we have entered into or are about to enter into with you personally; or (c) to comply with legal and regulatory requirements and requests. In rare, emergency situations we may use your personal data for your or someone else's vital interests. We generally do not rely on your consent for our EU processing other than in relation to the use of Cookies (see below) and to send you marketing emails, and we will inform you specifically when we seek to obtain this from you as well as your ability to withdraw that consent at any time. In some cases there may be overlap between these different basis.

Accordingly please note that we may undertake some EU Processing of your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above, where this is required or permitted by law, but if you would like more information about our basis of EU Processing please contact us at any time.  Unless otherwise required or permitted by law, before we begin EU Processing of your personal data for a purpose unrelated to those above, we will notify you and explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.

### How We Share Your Information

We may share your information, including personal information, as follows:

  * Users of Our Service. A key component of our Services is to connect you with other industry participants. If you choose to post a comment to one or our blog postings, then we collect the information that you make available through the blog. Any information that you post to our Site will be viewable by other visitors to our Site.
  * **_Event Attendees_.  **If you attend one of our events, we share your contact information with other attendees.
  * Affiliates. We disclose the information we collect from you to our affiliates or subsidiaries; however, if we do so, their use and disclosure of your personal information will be subject to this Policy.
  * Service Providers. We disclose the information we collect from you to third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform functions on our behalf.
  * Business Transfers. If we are acquired by or merged with another company, if we transfer assets to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the other company.
  * In Response to Legal Process. We also may disclose the information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena.
  * To Protect Us and Others. We also may disclose the information we collect from you where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use or this Policy, or as evidence in litigation in which Company is involved.
  * Aggregate Information. We may share aggregate information about users with third parties for marketing, advertising, research or similar purposes.

We provide the Services from the United States where the law may not provide the same level of data or privacy protection as your home territory.  Where, however, we are conducting EU Processing we will ensure appropriate safeguards are put in place to protect your personal data including through the use of specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe and European Commission adequacy decisions about certain countries, as applicable. You can find further information about these at <https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection_en>.

### Our Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms

We and our third party service providers use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to track information about your use of our Site or Services. We may combine this information with other personal information we collect from you (and our third party service providers may do so on our behalf).

Cookies.  Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Site and Services, while others are used to enable a faster log-in process or to allow us to track your activities at our Site and Service. There are two types of cookies: session and persistent cookies.

  * Session Cookies. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser or turn off your computer. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you during a session or while you are logged into the Site. This allows us to process your online transactions and requests and verify your identity, after you have logged in, as you move through our Site.
  * Persistent Cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer. We use persistent cookies to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity, and to display advertising both on our Site and on third-party sites.

Disabling Cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Visitors to our Site who disable cookies will be able to browse certain areas of the Site, but some features may not function.

### Clear GIFs, pixel tags and other technologies 

Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags), in connection with our Site to, among other things, track the activities of Site visitors, help us manage content, and compile statistics about Site usage. We and our third party service providers also use clear GIFs in HTML e-mails to our customers, to help us track e-mail response rates, identify when our e-mails are viewed, and track whether our e-mails are forwarded.

### Third Party Analytics

We use automated devices and applications, such as Google Analytics, to evaluate use of our Services. We also may use other analytic means to evaluate our Services. To learn more about Google’s privacy practices, please review the Google Privacy Policy at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/. You can also download the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on to prevent their data from being used by Google Analytics at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. We use these tools to help us improve our Services, performance and user experiences. These entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies to perform their services. We do not share your personal information with these third parties.

**Do Not Track**

Currently, our systems do not recognize browser “do-not-track” requests. You may, however, disable certain tracking as discussed in this section (e.g., by disabling cookies); you also may opt-out of targeted advertising by following the instructions in the Third Party Ad Network section.

### Third-Party Ad Networks

We use third parties such as network advertisers to display advertisements on our Sites, to assist us in displaying advertisements on third party websites, and to evaluate the success of our advertising campaigns. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to our Site as well as other websites. This enables us and these third parties to target advertisements by displaying ads for products and services in which you might be interested. Third party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information about your usage of our Site and our services, as well as aggregate or non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our Site and users of our service.

You may opt-out of many third-party ad networks, including those operated by members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”).  For more information regarding this practice by NAI members and DAA members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including how to opt-out of third-party ad networks operated by NAI and DAA members, please visit their respective websites: www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp (NAI) and www.aboutads.info/choices (DAA).

Opting out of one or more NAI member or DAA member networks (many of which will be the same) only means that those members no longer will deliver targeted content or ads to you. It does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content or ads on our Site or other websites. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, your NAI or DAA opt-out may no longer be effective. Additional information is available on NAI’s and DAA’s websites accessible by the above links.

User Generated Content

We invite you to post content on our Site, including your comments, pictures, and any other information that you would like to be available on our Site. If you post content to our Site, all of the information that you post will be available to all visitors to our Site. If you post your own content on our Site or Services, your posting may become public and Company cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Policy, the law, or your personal privacy.

### Third-Party Links

Our Site and Services may contain links to third-party websites. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Policy, but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those third party websites. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third party websites.

### Security of My Personal Information

We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures that are designed to provide an appropriate level of security taking into account the risks that are presented by the relevant processing, in particular from accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure of, or access to personal data transmitted, stored or otherwise processed.

You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your password, phone, and computer by, among other things, signing off after using a shared computer, choosing a robust password that nobody else knows or can easily guess, and keeping your log-in and password private.  You may be held legally responsible where you have failed to take reasonable care resulting in lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity.

For How Long Will You Use My Personal Information?

We will retain your personal information as long as necessary for purposes for which it was collected and used by us, as stated in this Privacy Policy.  Further, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we will retain and use your personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, maintain appropriate business records, and enforce our agreements.  Please contact us if you require more information about how we apply these criteria in specific cases.

### Access To My Personal Information

You may modify personal information that you have submitted by logging into your account and updating your profile information. Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Site or Application for a period of time.

### What Rights and Choices Do I Have Regarding Use of My Personal Information?

Email:  We may send periodic promotional to you (and if you are in the EU we will only do this if you have opted-in to receiving such promotions). You may opt-out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained in the e-mail. Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out requests. If you opt-out of receiving emails about recommendations or other information we think may interest you, we may still send you e-mails about your account or any Services you have requested or received from us.

Special Note to EU Data Subjects:  In respect of EU Processing you have the right to: (a) request a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it; (b) request that any incomplete or inaccurate personal data we hold about you is corrected; (c) request us to delete or remove the personal data we hold about you if we do not have a good reason to continue to process it (including if you successfully object to our processing below or where our processing was unlawful or erasure is required by law) note that if we cannot comply with your request for legal reasons we will notify these to you; (d) object to processing of your personal data if we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) which you believe are overridden by your interests, rights and freedoms - although we may be able to demonstrate otherwise, or where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes - see how to opt-out above; (e) request us to suspend the processing of your personal data if: (i) you want us to establish its accuracy; (ii) the processing in unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (iii) you want us to hold it in order to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or (iv) you have objected to our use of it but we need to verify whether we have an overriding legitimate grounds to use it; (e) request we transfer your personal data to you or to a third party in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format where you provided this automated information to us on the basis of consent or to perform a contract with you; and (f) withdraw consent at any time where we are relying on consent to process your personal data (but without affecting the lawfulness of any prior processing and subject to us advising you as to the impact if you withdraw your consent).

If you wish to exercise any of these rights please contact SEMI Europe Helmholtzstrasse 2-9 House D / 3rd floor 10587 Berlin, Germany.  You will not have to pay a fee unless your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive (or in which case we may refuse to comply). We may need to carry out verification checks including requesting identity information from you. We seek to comply with legitimate requests within one month but complex or multiple requests may take longer but we will keep you updated.

### Children Under 13

Our Services are not designed for children under 16. If we discover that a child under 16 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our systems.

### Contact Us

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our Services or would like to make a complaint, please contact us at [customerservice@semi.org](mailto:customerservice@semi.org).

You also have the right to lodge complaint with a supervisory data protection authority in respect of our EU Processing.

### Changes to this Policy

This Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Policy from time to time. We will post any changes to this Policy on our Site. If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on our Site, or sending a note to registered users at the email address of record.
